All the single ladies
All the single ladies Now
put your hands up
Up in the club (club)‚ we just
bro*****e up (up)‚ I am doing
my own little thing
Decided to dip (dip) and now
you wanna trip (trip)
′Cause another brother noticed me
I am up on him‚ he up on me
Don′t pay him any attention
Just cried my tears‚ for
three good years
You can′t get mad at me
′Cause if you li*****ed it‚ then you
should have put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
Don′t be mad once you
see that he want it
′Cause if you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you should
have put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you t be mad
once you see that he want it
Don′t be mad once you
see that he want it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
I got gloss on my lips‚
a man on my hips
Got me tighter in my carry on jeans
Acting up‚ drin***** in my cup
I can′t care less what you thin*****
I need no permission‚ did I mention
Don′t pay him any attention
′Cause you had your turn‚
and now you gonna learn
What it really feels li*****e to miss me
′Cause if you li*****ed it‚ then you
should have put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
Don′t be mad once you
see that he want it
′Cause if you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you
Don′t be mad once you
see that he want it
′Cause if you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
Don′t treat me to these
things of the world
I am not that *****ind of girl
Your love is what I prefer‚
what I deserve
Is a man that ma*****es me then ta*****es me
And delivers me to a destiny‚
to infinity and beyond
Pull me into your arms
Say I am the one you want
If you don′t‚ you′ll be alone
And li*****e a ghost I will be gone
All the single ladies‚(all
the single ladies)
All the single ladies‚ (all
All the single ladies Now
put your hands up
′Cause if you li*****ed it‚ then you
should have put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
Don′t be mad once you
see that he want it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you should
have put a ring on it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you
shoulda put a ring on it
Don′t be mad once you
see that he want it
If you li*****ed it‚ then you shoulda
put a ring on it‚ oh oh oh